What the hell
are you doing there?
It's so hot, and you're
just hanging out here!
Why are you out here?
See? You're getting dirty!
What's this on your hand?
[SOFT BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[RUSTLING]
Junifer Sampaga,
will you be mine?
[SOFT BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
If for you everything is fake,
there's nothing fake
about what I feel.
So... why not make it real?
Is this real?
Because...
I'm still a bit confused.
I love you.
And I'll marry you
in any church.
Even if I'm not a Rose by blood?
Even if your name is Junifer.
[CLICKS TONGUE] That was quick,
Fulgencio Nabong III.
Can I...
Can I process all of this first?
It's up to you.
I'll court you no matter
how long it takes.
Even if it's forever?
I'll make you fall in love
even if it takes forever.
Even if I have trouble hearing
and I stutter?
Even if you stutter so much.
What if...
I want all the leftover
rice for myself?
Well, that wasn't part
of the conversation.
[SNICKERS]
- I thought it was true love.
- [PING] I'm kidding!
We can share it, right?
As long as I don't lose you.
Just give me a chance
to be your boyfriend.
Fine!
As long as it's not fake, okay?
This time, it's not fake.
[JUNE GIGGLING]
[PLAYING "IKAW LANG" BY 1621]
My sister hope
forever!
I heard my son
was here.
Are You My Father?